Guide to the Brooks McNamara Papers MSS 162
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Subject Files, 69684
  - Minstrelsy: Student work., undated; 69919 (Box 17, Folder 303)
  - Minstrelsy: Photocopies, student work., undated; 69918 (Box 17, Folder 304)
  - Minstrelsy [book]: Correspondence, programs for "The Merry Muldoons"., undated; 69917 (Box 17, Folder 305)
  - Minstrelsy [misc.]: Photocopies, bibliographies., undated; 69916 (Box 17, Folder 306)
  - Minstrelsy [xeroxes]: Photocopies, student work., undated; 69915 (Box 17, Folder 307)
  - Minstrelsy [xeroxes]: Photocopies., undated; 69914 (Box 17, Folder 308)
  - Mummings I: Photocopies, bibliographies, course materials., undated; 69913 (Box 18, Folder 309)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233877
  - Mumming II: Student work., 1972-1976; 69912 (Box 18, Folder 310)
  - Mumming III: Article; 1982-3 issues of Roomer, The Newsletter of the Traditional Drama Research Group., undated; 69911 (Box 18, Folder 311)
  - Museums: Clipping, brochures; 1971 bulletin of the Philadelphia Old Town Historical Society., undated; 69910 (Box 18, Folder 312)
  - Music I: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence., undated; 69909 (Box 18, Folder 313)
  - Music II: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence, student work., undated; 69908 (Box 18, Folder 314)
  - Music Hall: Photocopies, articles; draft on Music Hall and Cabaret., undated; 69907 (Box 18, Folder 315)
  - [Music Halls to Movie Palaces (exhibition)]: Exhibition information, catalog., undated; 69906 (Box 18, Folder 316)
  - Music Programs I: Programs., undated; 69905 (Box 18, Folder 317)
  - Musical Programs II: Programs., undated; 69904 (Box 18, Folder 318)
  - Musical Theatre Papers I: Student work., undated; 69903 (Box 18, Folder 319)
  - Musical Theatre II: Clippings, articles, bibliographies, programs, fliers, correspondence, student work., undated; 69902 (Box 18, Folder 320)
  - Musical Theatre III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, student work; articles and publicity on Miles Kreuger and the Institute of the American Musical; 1921 issue of The World Magazine., undated; 69901 (Box 18, Folder 321)
  - [Musical Theatre Archive], undated; 69900 (Box 18, Folder 322)
  - [Musical Theatre in America Conference], undated; 69899 (Box 18, Folder 323)
  - Red, Hot, and Blue! The Rise of the American Musical: Exhibition information, photographs from the National Portrait Gallery., undated; 69898 (Box 18, Folder 324)
  - Musicals [misc.]: Photocopies., undated; 69897 (Box 18, Folder 325)
  - Night Clubs I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, fliers, advertisements, publicity materials., undated; 69896 (Box 19, Folder 326)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233885
  - Night Clubs I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, fliers, advertisements, publicity materials. MAKE NEW Night Clubs II: Articles, photocopies, student work, bibliography., undated; 69895 (Box 19, Folder 327)
  - [New Years/Christmas]: Photocopies., undated; 69894 (Box 19, Folder 328)
  - Novel [source material]: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence., undated; 69893 (Box 19, Folder 329)
  - Opera Houses: Clippings, articles, postcards, bibliography; issues of American Society of Theatre Research Newsletter; press kit on renovation of Wilmington, DE opera house., undated; 69892 (Box 19, Folder 330)
  - Optical and Mechanical I: Clippings, articles, fliers, bibliographic notes; cards from mechanical fortune telling machine (?); NYC folding souvenir slide viewer., undated; 69891 (Box 19, Folder 331)
  - Optical and Mechanical Entertainment II: Clippings, photocopies, articles, fliers, correspondence; 2 templates for cut-out paper theatres., undated; 69890 (Box 19, Folder 332)
  - Oral History: Various interviews by BM and others for project, Vanishing Theatre: an Oral History of Popular Entertainment in America, introduction by BM., 1972; 69889 (Box 19, Folder 333)
  - Oral History [misc], undated; 69888 (Box 19, Folder 334)
  - Outsider Art: Clipping; flyer on graffiti symposium (1996)., 1996, 1997; 69887 (Box 19, Folder 335)
  - Pageants I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, course materials, student work., undated; 69886 (Box 19, Folder 336)
  - Pageants II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work and bibliographies; lists of public processions/festivals in NY and in U.S., undated; 69885 (Box 19, Folder 337)
  - Pageants III: Various souvenir programs for festivals and parades in U.S.; 1976 and 1977 press releases for Macy's Day Parade., 1975-1977; 69884 (Box 19, Folder 338)
  - Pageants IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work and bibliographies; July 1929 issue of "The Sphere: A London Newsletter.", undated; 69883 (Box 19, Folder 339)
  - Pageants V: Souvenir programs, pamphlets, brochures, unpublished manuscripts., undated; 69882 (Box 19, Folder 340)
  - Pageants VI: Student paper., undated; 69881 (Box 19, Folder 341)
  - Pageants VII: Programs, brochures, course material., undated; 69880 (Box 20, Folder 342)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233893
  - Pageants VIII: Clippings, photocopies, programs, photographs, fliers, correspondence; Institute of Outdoor Drama newsletters., undated; 69879 (Box 20, Folder 343)
  - Pageant IX: Draft of BM article on pageantry for Theatre Crafts Magazine (1975), correspondence., 69878 (Box 20, Folder 344)
  - Panoramas and Dioramas I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, photographs, correspondence, panoramas, bibliography, student work., undated; 69877 (Box 20, Folder 345)
  - Panoramas and Dioramas II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, correspondence, panoramas, bibliography, student work; BM notes; catalog from The Swann Collection of Caricature and Cartoon., undated; 69876 (Box 20, Folder 346)
  - Pantomime I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, correspondence, photographs, bibliographies, student work., undated; 69875 (Box 20, Folder 347)
  - Pantomime II: Clippings, articles, programs, fliers, correspondence, bibliographies; 1965 issue of Educational Theatre Journal., undated; 69874 (Box 20, Folder 348)
  - Parades I: Clipping, student work; questionnaires on Macy's Day Parade., undated; 69873 (Box 20, Folder 349)
  - Parades II: Student work., undated; 69872 (Box 20, Folder 350)
  - Parades III: Student work., 1977; 69871 (Box 20, Folder 351)
  - Parades IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, photographs, student work., undated; 69870 (Box 20, Folder 352)
  - Parades V: Clippings, photocopies, programs, fliers, unpublished manuscript; poster for 1983 Coney Island Mermaid Day Parade., undated; 69869 (Box 20, Folder 353)
  - Parades: McNamara Paper: Drafts, notes., undated; 69868 (Box 20, Folder 354)
  - Parks: Clippings, photocopy of 1873 plan for Central Park., undated; 69867 (Box 20, Folder 355)
  - Parlour Entertainments: Clippings, articles, photocopies, notes, scripts, pamphlets, brochures, student papers., undated; 69866 (Box 20, Folder 356)
  - Passion Play: Veronica's Veil: Clipping, souvenir program., undated; 69865 (Box 20, Folder 357)
  - Peep Shows: Articles, artist's brochure., undated; 69864 (Box 20, Folder 358)
  - Penny Gaff: Photocopies., undated; 69863 (Box 20, Folder 359)
  - [Performance Spaces: misc.]: Photocopies, articles, BM drafts., undated; 69862 (Box 20, Folder 360)
  - Physical Theatre: Articles, unpublished papers., undated; 69861 (Box 20, Folder 361)
  - Physical Theatre: Anti-Realist to WWII: Student papers., undated; 69860 (Box 20, Folder 362)
  - Piers and Boardwalks: Clippings, postcard., undated; 69859 (Box 20, Folder 363)
  - Pilgrimage: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student paper; "Little Guide Book of Lourdes.", undated; 69858 (Box 21, Folder 364)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233901
  - Playboy Environments: June 11, 1972 issue of The New York Times Magazine., 69857 (Box 21, Folder 365)
  - Plays: Clippings, article, photocopies, programs; catalog of "Original Rare Manuscripts, History of the American Theater: From 1789 to 1974"; play list of 19th and early 20th c. American plays "with ethnic characterizations.", undated; 69856 (Box 21, Folder 366)
  - [Plays - misc.], undated; 69855 (Box 21, Folder 367)
  - [Plays - misc.], undated; 69854 (Box 21, Folder 368)
  - [Play scripts: "The Tourists" and "The Road Up the Mountain"], undated; 69853 (Box 21, Folder 369)
  - Political Theatre: Photocopies, student paper., undated; 69852 (Box 21, Folder 370)
  - Popular Entertainment: Articles, photocopies, fliers, exhibition catalogs, student and faculty work; BM notes and project description, Brockton Arts Center exhibition "American Pastimes"; BM manuscript on popular entertainment directed to the American Theatre Association [now defunct]., undated; 69851 (Box 21, Folder 371)
  - Popular Entertainments II: Clippings, articles, conference programs, bibliographic information and indexes of source materials, student work; conference program "On the Aesthetics of Everyday Life" (1991); The New Yorker index (1992); unpublished draft of article on religious kitsch., undated; 69850 (Box 21, Folder 372)
  - Popular Entertainment III: Clippings, conference programs, course syllabi, bibliographies, student work; draft of Marvin Carlson talk "The State of the Profession" (1989); draft "Confusing Pleasures," Barbara Kirshenblatt-Gimblett., undated; 69849 (Box 21, Folder 373)
  - Popular Entertainments IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, conference programs, bibliographies, course materials, student work., undated; 69848 (Box 21, Folder 374)
  - Popular Entertainments V: Clippings, articles, photocopies, conference programs, bibliographic information, course materials, student work., undated; 69847 (Box 21, Folder 375)
  - Popular Entertainments Book: Correspondence, drafts, notes; ideas for popular entertainment book by BM and John Towsen., 1974; 69846 (Box 21, Folder 376)
  - Popular Entertainment and the Avant-Garde: Clippings, articles, photocopies, bibliographies, student paper, catalogs; proposals for BM popular entertainment anthology and oral history project., undated; 69845 (Box 21, Folder 377)
  - Popular Entertainment - UG Drama Panel: Print-out copy of BM questioning John Towsen and Jeff Sheriden, 1979; 69844 (Box 21, Folder 378)
  - Popular Entertainment - Newsletter Possibilities: Newsletters, conference programs, book announcements., undated; 69843 (Box 21, Folder 379)
  - Popular Entertainment [misc.]: Photocopies., undated; 69842 (Box 22, Folder 380)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233919
  - [Popular Entertainments] Conference on the History of Popular Entertainment: Correspondence, meeting minutes, drafts, abstracts, newsletters., undated; 69841 (Box 22, Folder 381)
  - [Popular Entertainments] International Symposium on Popular Entertainment I: Correspondence, meeting minutes, drafts, abstracts, conference programs., undated; 69840 (Box 22, Folder 382)
  - [Popular Entertainments] International Symposium on Popular Entertainment II: Correspondence, International Federation for Theatre Research meeting minutes and announcements., 1985-1987; 69839 (Box 22, Folder 383)
  - Popular Playwriting I: Student paper, flier., undated; 69838 (Box 22, Folder 384)
  - Popular Playwriting II: Articles, photocopies, student work., undated; 69837 (Box 22, Folder 385)
  - Press Agentry: Student work., undated; 69836 (Box 22, Folder 386)
  - Producers: Student work., undated; 69835 (Box 22, Folder 387)
  - Psychic: Flier., undated; 69834 (Box 22, Folder 388)
  - Public Celebrations: Clippings, conference program., 1996; 69833 (Box 22, Folder 389)
  - Puppets I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, programs, postcards, drafts., undated; 69832 (Box 22, Folder 390)
  - Puppets II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, programs, correspondence, course syllabus, drafts, BM notes., undated; 69831 (Box 22, Folder 391)
  - Puppets III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, programs, student work., undated; 69830 (Box 22, Folder 392)
  - Puppet Papers I: Student papers., undated; 69829 (Box 22, Folder 393)
  - Puppet Papers II: Student papers., undated; 69828 (Box 22, Folder 394)
  - Radical Theatre I: Articles, photocopies, correspondence, student work., undated; 69827 (Box 23, Folder 395)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233927
  - Radical Theatre II: Articles, photocopies, conference programs, bibliographies, student work., undated; 69826 (Box 23, Folder 396)
  - Radical Theatre III: Newsletters, conference programs, student programs., undated; 69825 (Box 23, Folder 397)
  - Radio I: Clippings, articles, radio program listings, course materials, student work., undated; 69824 (Box 23, Folder 398)
  - Radio II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, conference papers and programs, student work., undated; 69823 (Box 23, Folder 399)
  - Radio City Music Hall: Clippings, programs, fliers., undated; 69822 (Box 23, Folder 400)
  - Radio City Music Hall: Clippings, programs, fliers., undated; 69821 (Box 23, Folder 401)
  - Radio City Music Hall II: Clippings, programs, fliers., undated; 69820 (Box 23, Folder 402)
  - Radio City Music Hall II: Programs, fliers., undated; 69819 (Box 23, Folder 403)
  - [Reinhardt, Max]: Photocopies., undated; 69818 (Box 23, Folder 404)
  - Resorts: Clippings, articles, photocopies., undated; 69817 (Box 23, Folder 405)
  - Resorts II (summer): Clippings, articles, photocopies, student paper., undated; 69816 (Box 23, Folder 406)
  - Revivalism: Clippings, article, student paper., undated; 69815 (Box 23, Folder 407)
  - Revue I: Articles, photocopies, programs, student work., undated; 69814 (Box 23, Folder 408)
  - Revues II: Clippings, Radio City Music Hall programs and magazines, book proposal., undated; 69813 (Box 24, Folder 409)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233935
  - Rituals I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, bibliographies, paper drafts, notes., undated; 69812 (Box 24, Folder 410)
  - Ritual II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, conference papers., undated; 69811 (Box 24, Folder 411)
  - Ritual III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, fliers, programs, student work., undated; 69810 (Box 24, Folder 412)
  - Ritual Papers I: Student papers., undated; 69809 (Box 24, Folder 413)
  - Ritual (Funeral): Typescript of book., undated; 69808 (Box 24, Folder 414)
  - Role Playing: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, fliers, student work., undated; 69807 (Box 24, Folder 415)
  - Roller Skating: March 1980 issue of Smithsonian magazine., 69806 (Box 24, Folder 416)
  - Rodeo: Clippings, fliers., undated; 69805 (Box 24, Folder 417)
  - Scene Designers: Student paper., undated; 69804 (Box 24, Folder 418)
  - Sceneography of Popular Entertainments I: BM typescripts, drafts, notes; article, photocopies., undated; 69803 (Box 24, Folder 419)
  - Scenography of Popular Entertainment II: Living Theatre schematic., undated; 69540 (Box 35, Folder 676)
  - Sceneography of Popular Entertainment II: Photographs., undated; 69802 (Box 24, Folder 420)
  - Scenography of Popular Entertainment II: Photographs and wall labels., undated; 69539 (Box 35, Folder 677)
  - Sceneography of Popular Entertainments III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence, student work., undated; 69801 (Box 24, Folder 421)
  - Showboats: Clippings, fliers; cookbook "Showboats, Sugar, and Spice.", undated; 69800 (Box 24, Folder 422)
  - [Soap Opera]: Photocopy., undated; 69799 (Box 24, Folder 423)
  - Spectacle: Clippings, articles, photocopies, program, student work., undated; 69798 (Box 24, Folder 424)
  - [Speech, Jokes, Bits]: Photocopies., undated; 69797 (Box 24, Folder 425)
  - Spiritualism: Student work, flier., undated; 69796 (Box 24, Folder 426)
  - Sports I: Student paper, clipping., undated; 69795 (Box 24, Folder 427)
  - Sport II: Clipping, program, flier, student paper., undated; 69794 (Box 24, Folder 428)
  - Sports III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, brochure, student work., undated; 69793 (Box 24, Folder 429)
  - Storytelling: Article., 1986; 69792 (Box 24, Folder 430)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, Index: BM notes., undated; 69791 (Box 25, Folder 431)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233943
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, Sources and Bibliographies: Correspondence, photocopies, bibliographies, BM notes., undated; 69790 (Box 25, Folder 432)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 1-25: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence, BM notes, photographs and negatives., undated; 69789 (Box 25, Folder 433)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 26-50: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work, BM notes., undated; 69788 (Box 25, Folder 434)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 51-75: Clippings, articles, photocopies., undated; 69787 (Box 25, Folder 435)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 76-99: Clippings, articles, photocopies, BM notes; dictionary of Cockney Slang and Rhyming Slang., undated; 69786 (Box 25, Folder 436)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 100-124: Photocopies., undated; 69785 (Box 25, Folder 437)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 125-149: Photocopies., undated; 69784 (Box 25, Folder 438)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 150-174: Photocopies., undated; 69783 (Box 25, Folder 439)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 175-199: Photocopies., undated; 69782 (Box 25, Folder 440)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 200-224: Photocopies., undated; 69781 (Box 25, Folder 441)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 225-249: Clippings, photocopies., undated; 69780 (Box 25, Folder 442)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 250-274: Clippings, photocopies, articles; BM interview with Percy Press., undated; 69779 (Box 25, Folder 443)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research, 275-300: Clippings, photocopies, articles, bibliographies., undated; 69778 (Box 25, Folder 444)
  - Street Entertainments: London Research [misc.]: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, bibliographies., undated; 69777 (Box 25, Folder 445)
  - Street Entertainers: Clippings, articles, photocopies, conference programs, correspondence; BM drafts., undated; 69776 (Box 26, Folder 446)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233950
  - Street Entertainment I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student paper., undated; 69775 (Box 26, Folder 447)
  - Street Entertainment II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, photographs and postcards, BM drafts., undated; 69774 (Box 26, Folder 448)
  - Street Entertainment III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence., undated; 69773 (Box 26, Folder 449)
  - Street Entertainment IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, correspondence, postcards; BM proposal, "Theatre in the Streets: An Illustrated History of the Street Entertainer.", undated; 69772 (Box 26, Folder 450)
  - Commercial Culture Seminar: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work; photocopy of BM proposal, "Theatre in the Streets: An Illustrated History of the Street Entertainer.", undated; 69771 (Box 26, Folder 451)
  - Street Entertainment Pictures: Photographs., undated; 69770 (Box 26, Folder 452)
  - Street Entertainment [Sally Harrison]: Correspondence and typescript., undated; 69769 (Box 26, Folder 453)
  - Street Performance: Clippings, articles, photocopies, poster, correspondence, student work., undated; 69768 (Box 26, Folder 454)
  - Summer Stock and Dinner Theatres: Clipping, poster., undated; 69767 (Box 26, Folder 455)
  - Sword Swallowing: Clipping, interview transcript., undated; 69766 (Box 26, Folder 456)
  - Tableaux: Student work, BM notes., undated; 69765 (Box 26, Folder 457)
  - Tattooing: Clippings, articles, photocopies., undated; 69764 (Box 26, Folder 458)
  - Television: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work., undated; 69763 (Box 26, Folder 459)
  - Tent Rep.: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, correspondence, bibliographies, student papers; NEH application for a Tent Show exhibition., undated; 69762 (Box 26, Folder 460)
  - Tent Show I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, scripts, correspondence., undated; 69761 (Box 26, Folder 461)
  - Tent Show II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, scripts, correspondence., undated; 69760 (Box 26, Folder 462)
  - Testimony: Clipping, press release., undated; 69759 (Box 26, Folder 463)
  - Theatre Papers I: Student work, bibliographies., 1974-1985; 69758 (Box 27, Folder 464)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233968
  - Theatre Papers II: Photocopies, student work, bibliographies., 1978-1987; 69757 (Box 27, Folder 465)
  - Theatres I: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69756 (Box 27, Folder 466)
  - Theatres II: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69755 (Box 27, Folder 467)
  - Theatres III: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theatre listings, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69754 (Box 27, Folder 468)
  - Theatres IV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures, student work., undated; 69753 (Box 27, Folder 469)
  - Theatres V: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69752 (Box 27, Folder 470)
  - Theatres VI: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69751 (Box 27, Folder 471)
  - Theatres VII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69750 (Box 27, Folder 472)
  - Theatres VIII: Souvenir programs for historic theatres, clipping., undated; 69749 (Box 27, Folder 473)
  - Theatres IX: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69748 (Box 27, Folder 474)
  - Theatres X: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures., undated; 69747 (Box 27, Folder 475)
  - Theatres XI: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures, BM notes., undated; 69746 (Box 27, Folder 476)
  - Theatres XII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, souvenir programs for renovated historic theatres, brochures, correspondence., undated; 69745 (Box 27, Folder 477)
  - Theatres XIII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theater-related catalogs, listings, programs, brochures, newsletters, student work., undated; 69744 (Box 28, Folder 478)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233976
  - Theatres XIV: Articles, photocopies, photographs, correspondence, student paper., undated; 69743 (Box 28, Folder 479)
  - Theatres XV: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theater-related catalogs, listings, programs., undated; 69742 (Box 28, Folder 480)
  - Theatres XVI: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theater-related catalogs, listings, programs., undated; 69741 (Box 28, Folder 481)
  - Theatres XVII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, student work., undated; 69740 (Box 28, Folder 482)
  - Theatres XVIII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theater-related catalogs, listings, programs., undated; 69739 (Box 28, Folder 483)
  - Theatres XIX: Clippings, articles, photocopies, newsletters, correspondence., undated; 69738 (Box 28, Folder 484)
  - Theatres XX: Clippings, articles, photocopies, programs, newsletters; theatre assembly kit, "Empire Theatre.", undated; 69737 (Box 28, Folder 485)
  - Theatres XXI: Student work, programs., undated; 69736 (Box 28, Folder 486)
  - Theatres XXII: Photocopies, BM papers on theatres, bibliography., undated; 69735 (Box 28, Folder 487)
  - Theatres XXIII: Clippings, articles, photocopies, theatre brochure, student paper; "The London Stage: A Calendar of Performances, 1800-1900"; photographs of Frank Lloyd Wright theatres., undated; 69734 (Box 28, Folder 488)
  - Theatres XXIV: Photocopies, Edward Hopper catalog., undated; 69733 (Box 28, Folder 489)